It's coming, it's coming. They are coming. Yes, they are coming. They are both coming.
It is delivered in.
Poof, you are young, aren't you?
I don't know.
Did he come on both Saturday and Sunday?
Yes, he was.
I couldn't tell if he was a member or a fan, you know?
It was so chaotic.
Even the people in charge were waving their penlights.
Oh, I see. I could see quite a bit.
I could see a lot of the parents.
It wasn't Hoshi's father or anything.
There were some here and there with my mom.
Really?
She's always saying her daughter's in trouble.
Oh, hi.
Now you sound like the lady from the park.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I looked like a bunch of ladies in the park.
Nice to meet you.
Please give my regards to you.
So, well, it was cold today, wasn't it?
Yes, indeed.
Yesterday was a little colder than today, wasn't it?
It was extremely cold.
But I don't know if it's because of global warming or not,
But, I don't know if it's global warming or not, but I am sure that winters are not so severe compared to when I was a child.
I see.
It's a warm winter.
When I was a child, my breath was definitely frozen when I was in elementary school.
In the morning, so, jaja, jaja, Mitaka. So I always went there first thing in the morning, and I'd just throw a rock over there.
No, there's nothing wrong with that. Break it. Sure. I want to break it.
I used to freeze every day. That hasn't happened recently. Certainly not. It doesn't freeze very often.
This neighborhood doesn't freeze very often.
Why is that? No, no, no, anyway, it's very cold in the morning.
It's cold.
Please be careful. You sound like an FM station. I just wanted to ask you to be careful. You sound like an FM station.
We are not FM Yokohama.
Well, that's the way it is, so let's get on with the program.
Please let's proceed with the program.
Oh, yes, before that, I would like to introduce Mr. Gan Bandani.
Gan Bandani. Please give my regards to you.
Welcome to Japan.
Thank you very much.
Well, well, well, well.
Well, let's begin.
Well, first of all, it's February 2nd today.
Tomorrow is the Setsubun Festival!
I love ehomaki!
I love ehoumaki!
I love eating them!
I'm a messy person and it's fine when I was a kid, but now I'm the one who throws the beans and picks them up myself.
What are you doing?
I'm a match pump, right?
Setsubun is a time of seasonal transition from midwinter to spring.
I was running... right... that's why...
Seriously, everything I'm thinking about is written on the net.
I'm reading it, and you said you saw that I wrote it with the holder...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, actually, I didn't know that either.
I thought snow was a seasonal word.
I thought it just meant... "Setsubun"...
I don't know...
It's supposed to ward off the evil spirits of the ogres that appear at the change of seasons.
In this sense, bean sprinkling is done...
The beans are scattered while shouting "Fuku wa uchi wa uchi" and "Oni wa soto".
If the evil spirit is here, we want to get rid of it, too!
We want to get rid of it!
So we prepared the beans!
It's been a long time since I've done this!
Tettere!
Here you go!
It looks like this.
Beans are just beans. Beans are beans, though.
They smell so good.
Beans.
I'm going to roll these up.
Are you sure you want to do this?
No, no, no, no. We have to get rid of the evil.
Why not? Let's do it.
Are you sure?
Then, let's do the Fukuauchi.
You want to do it from the outside in?
From the inside out. - From the outside in.
Can we do it all outward?
I think it's fine like this, right?
But that one!
What are you dodging?
If you do it this way...
That was fast.
Don't be so surprised.
It's not like I'm throwing bombs or anything. Beans.
He was a boxer.
But you know what? He's like an ogre. I'm just an ogre.
Is that okay? I don't want to be an ogre.
Without reservation?
I mean, not just a little, but as an adult with a moral compass.
With a sense of ethics.
Ethics?
Okay, I'll go.
Oh, no.
boo boo car chat. sound is outside.
Haaaaah!
huh?
Thank you very much
Uzenyon aruzaimasu!
Good day to you, see you again ★
Zeraru. It's over!
Tomitake, it's over!
Tomitake, it's over! Tomitake! It's over!
Ouch! This isn't a pachinko parlor!
Now the good fortune goes within!
So, now that we've got rid of the evil spirits... and the beans have become so good...
But the last part is the most important.
You eat as many beans as you are old enough to receive medicine...
I'm so excited!
Yes, I've got it, here it is...
It's like water for firewood.
Okay, count 16
He's blabbing to make it quicker.
Thank you very much... but the lotter is 20, 25, 16, 16...
But when you get to 123456, you have to wait a bit for 57 pieces.
Hm...
Hugh? informação room 151718
11526 at the time ako
31323 sı 5
I'm not sure if this is how it's going to be, but I'm going to wait a bit.
I can't get it in one hand.
This is great...
It's like this, isn't it?
oh, right...
Here, eat this, okay?
I'm going to eat the baibli that's talking about zakzakzakzakzakzakzakzakzakzakzak
Ahhhh, beans are so good!
Mame-raun delicious!
This is good. It's so good, it's gonna take all the water out of your body.
That's right, isn't it?
57 pieces are hard... but this is the most important thing.
This is the last one.
Mmm.
I'm going to deliver the beans.
Yes, you!
Counting the years. Counting the years.
One too many. Yeah, that's one too many.
I guess one of us has to eat more than the other, huh?
I can't swallow this at all.
It's delicious.
Yeah, it's good.
Thank you for the food.
Thank you for dinner.
That was fast.
How did this happen?
I'm eating so much food.
But we're almost done.
But you know what? You're not swallowing at all.
I'm just putting it in.
Yum!
It's true, they say it's still January 17th, but it's still January 17th.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'll clean it up later.
It's like they're attracted to it. It sounds like that.
I'm eating it now.
They're coming in!
They say it's just a branch of surrealism.
Oh, my gosh, a New Year's gift for you, Mr. Brandani!
I got a New Year's gift!
Peace sign, you gave us a level charge!
Thank you so much!
I wonder which way they'll eat it this year... North Tohoku, North Tohoku...
North Tohoku? North Tohoku?
I think it says "North, North, North Tohoku". North Tohoku?
Which way is north?
This way?
I don't get it.
North? I don't know.
I think it's east-northeast because the sign is hidden.
Northeast? Northeast isn't a tourist town. Let's go have fun.
I love it! You're not allowed to talk until you've finished eating, right?
And I heard you can't cut it off.
You have to eat them as they are.
I see. Oh, I see.
Well, I'll see you later with the beans.
Thank you very much.
You'll be safe this year, that's for sure.
I'm sorry.
So, now that we've got that out of the way...
Yes! You have a picture? Yes! Here's a picture from me.
This one! Christmasy? Yes! I went to this Christmas market with my mom.
I went to the Christmas market with my mom. The one with the red bricks? That's right! That's right!
By chance! I met Salmon and Mr. Atsusingo.
And wow! I was like, "Wow!
I noticed them at first, but
But they didn't notice me.
I said to them, "Thanks for your hard work!
They were both at the same distance from me! Wow! They were flying!
They were flying. They're so close.
The people around us were a little surprised.
I was that surprised. We took their picture.
It was amazing. It was so beautiful.
I think it's a great story that Nami Iwaban went to the Christmas market with her mom.
What were you two doing?
It's nice.
It's okay to go to a Christmas market. I'm not saying it's wrong, but what were you doing?
I was just having fun and filming on TikTok and stuff. I hope I get some work done. Good, good, good.
He was really nice to me. We were talking about athletes.
I was talking about how much I missed that athlete, and he said, "Good work.
And I was like, "Oh my God," and then he said, "Good work." And I was like, "Oh my God," and I was like, "Good work.
It was only for a second or two, but the moment we connected with each other, it was like...
Wow! Wow!
It was nostalgic, wasn't it?
Wait a minute, it's not a date with Shingo, it's not a date with Shingo, it's not a date with Shingo.
Well, it's like we're already living together. Even if it's a live-in girlfriend, I definitely don't want to live with her.
I'm telling you this, I really don't think we can live together.
Well, even if they don't live together, they still love each other.
I think it's fine.
By the way, we also have two photos from a lighter side.
Let's start with this one... this way... I went to a new sauna called "NAGOMI" in the morning, which a viewer told me about.
I went to a sauna in the morning that a viewer told me about.
I've just been filming a little bit in front of the train station, right?
No, it was a sauna.
It was a sauna that had just been built, so it was really clean.
I brought my watch, you know? But I messed up the sync a little bit, so it didn't come out right, so...
It's not a self-evaluation, it's just a self-evaluation, but it was really nice.
They had three saunas.
I had a sauna with self-laundry and also the main sauna, and it was really nice.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. But really, how many saunas do you go to?
Well, I'm thinking of limiting it a little bit this year.
Why, why, why?
It's kind of tiring.
Oh, it's such a strenuous activity.
It takes a lot of energy. I wish I could go the next day when there is nothing going on.
Yes, yes, yes. That's right.
Well, I think it's also a matter of how you get in.
Well, after hearing your comment, I was hoping it would cool down soon.
No, no, no. Why, why, why, why, why.
Because we're only talking about sauna. Really.
We only talk about sauna every time.
No, but it's really good.
I understand. I understand.
I understand. I understand. There are different facilities.
That's for sure.
There were two kinds of water baths.
There was a flexible water bath and a single water bath.
Water bath of water temperature It is not a cold one. I couldn't even put it in for 10 seconds. It was so cold.
I don't want to go through all that trouble. Why would I do that if I paid for it?
But that's what's important.
But you know... the girls are saying that too... they are saying that... right?
I think the sauna rate for Ebichu is already over 50%.
Thank you for watching.
I think most of the older sisters go to the sauna.
And one more sauna meal after the sauna, Sanmeshi!
This time I had a big bowl of curry!
The beauty of sauna is that you enter the world of the senses when you're ready.
Here you go! Yes, sir.
That's why I can hear music so well, and I'm so happy about everything.
So the senses? Taste? It sharpens my sense of taste, so the food tastes better.
That's right. So, I even set up a shamisen set.
It was a really nice sauna. Thank you for telling us.
You know...
When food tastes good, it's probably a happy time.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who go to the sauna.
I'm sure there are a lot of people who go to saunas.
I wish
can me
But you are an Edokko, aren't you? So, I have an announcement to make here.
The details of the Odate Uchideburu to be held on March 31st have been decided, so I'd like to make an announcement.
I would like to inform you all of the details. First of all, the performers will be Ebitu-chan and the other two members of Ebitu 66.
The two members of "66" and myself.
The heavy part is that there may be some big names, like Shohei Ohtani or something like that.
Like Shohei Otani.
On the contrary, it was awkward.
He came all the way from the U.S. and said, "Oh my God...
No, yes, and...
And the content, yes, it's almost settled.
We're going to do a school skit! I'm looking forward to it!
The title of the skit has already been decided.
So, Sohbi will be our teacher and educate us. Yes, I have a lot to learn from Sohbi.
Yes, indeed!
What is it? Did he teach you anything? But you're probably the most serious of all.
That's just an appearance, right? You are very serious, Mr. Subie.
We unserious people have to learn.
It's so tight and beautiful.
I thought it might be the date change.
You can't move it by a few minutes.
That's how beautiful it is.
I don't even know what the border is, but it's something.
I'm thinking of doing a story about a teacher who's foot fire erupts.
And, um...
Oh, my God, it's been 7 whole years as of March 31st, Kannai Devil!
That's great!
Let's see... Let's see...
Seven years is not that long.
No, it's a long time. Seven years is just a blink of an eye.
Seven years is a very short time...
But if you look carefully, it looks like you don't need to read that part.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And you said that I didn't have to read it.
Scary, scary, scary... and... Here it comes!
The Kamen Layer... you all came to see me once.
He came once, and I'm sure we'll find out more about him there.
We'll also be presenting a special version of the BFF show, as well as a live performance by Evichu and 66.
And of course, we'll have Evichu and 66 performing live.
And of course, we'll have Evichu and 66's live performance as well.
A new season is starting the next week, a new year, a new year.
I hope we can announce a new opening song for the new season.
Looking forward to it for a year? A year?
One year? Thank you very much.
And now...
And... the so-called "Ozeki"...
Yes?
We'll be selling seats to the general public soon.
This will start on the 20th of January.
If you have time, I'd like you all to come.
Also, as we did last time...
We'll be handing out raffle tickets to those who enter, and if a winner is chosen, we'll give them a chance to win one of the flips we've written on.
We wrote a lot of flips, including the one for the creatures, and we also wrote a lot of flips for ours.
The one with the "*" on top.
I'm going to show you...
We used them so much that we put them to sleep and didn't show them to the public.
I wrote about Hibari Miura for a week, so please don't miss it
I've been writing for a week, so please don't miss it.
It's like a triangular Fuji.
Please be sure to come and join us!
We've received a lot of people who have managed to get lip seats.
We've received a lot of "Devil Ticket Master" and "Devil Charge" from Mr. Niti.
Thank you, Mr. Niti.
It's nice to have a place where you can meet everyone at least once a year.
That's what happiness is, isn't it? I guess that's what happiness is all about.
BAU
Bau.
Master, master, Bau! I Bau! Bau! Yeah! I got Bau!
Am I supposed to be happy I did it? When he says "Bow," he's complimenting you.
It's a little bit like, you know, translating into, "Wow, that's great.
Yes.
I say congratulations to Mr. Nagaoka, and congratulations to you for 7 years, thank you very much.
Devilchic really sends us something every week.
It's like a story a day.
So, Devilch, are you okay? Eating all that high-calorie food.
But I eat food every day.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's the same thing, isn't it? I'm a moderate eater, so I'm fine.
Well, since we're ending the live streaming, let's have a rare night out!
Rare knights, please!
Wait a minute... we're presenting...
Fire in the gundam!
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much!
I got a bruise on the opposite side.